A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; 1970-1982; 1.9; 90.59 Cubic Feet; 224 letter-size document boxes, 10 legal-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, 1 half-legal document box, and 1 15-11.5 oversized document box
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Douglass Creative Arts Center, Inc. - "American Rag" Publication, 1979-1981 1983 (Box 148, Folder 1022)
        Frederick Douglass Creative Arts Center, Inc.
      - Emory University - Cameron, Rondo, 1979-1983 (Box 148, Folder 1023)
        Folder 1023 contains Evaluation
      - English-Speaking Union - Television Series, 1980-1984 (Box 148, Folder 1024-1025)
        Folder 1024 contains Evaluation
      - English-Speaking Union - Television Series: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 148, Folder 1026-1027)
      - Etra, William and Etra, Louise, 1976-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1028)
      - Etra, William and Etra, Louise (Evaluation), 1977 (Box 149, Folder 1029)
      - Exploratorium, 1975-1980 (Box 149, Folder 1030-1031)
        Grant made to the Palace of Arts and Science Foundation, corporate name of the organization of which The Exploratorium is a part
      - Exploratorium (Evaluation), 1977, 1981, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1032)
      - Fink, Kenneth, 1975-1977, 1979-1982 (Box 149, Folder 1033)
      - Fink, Kenneth (Evaluation), 1977, 1981, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1034)
      - Friedman, Raymond, 1980-1983 (Box 150, Folder 1035)
        Folder 1035 contains Evaluation
      - Fry, Amelia R., 1979-1983 (Box 150, Folder 1036)
        Folder 1036 contains Evaluation
      - George Washington University - Van Der Zee Photography Book, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1037)
      - George Washington University - Van Der Zee Photography Book (Evaluation), 1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1038)
      - Global Village - "Our Children" Film, 1979-1983, 1986 (Box 150, Folder 1039)
      - Greenfield, Amy, 1979-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 150, Folder 1040)
        Folder 1040 contains Evaluation
      - Gremp, David, 1978-1983, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 1041)
        Folder 1041 contains Evaluation
      - Gremp, David: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 151, Folder 1042)
      - Harvard University - Ethics and Public Policy, 1977-1982 (Box 151, Folder 1043)
      - Harvard University - Ethics and Public Policy (Evaluation), 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 151, Folder 1044)
      - Hoiby, Lee, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 1045)
        Folder 1045 contains Evaluation
      - Images, A Festival of the Arts, Inc. - Artists-in-Residence, 1977-1980 (Box 151, Folder 1046)
      - Images, A Festival of the Arts, Inc. - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 1047)
      - Indiana University - Semiotics, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 1048)
        Folder 1048 contains Evaluation
      - Just Above Midtown, 1975-1978, 1980, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 1049, Box 152, Folder 1050-1051)
      - Just Above Midtown (Evaluation), 1976-1977 (Box 152, Folder 1052)
      - Kansas City Art Institute - Video Curriculum, 1973-1981 (Box 152, Folder 1053-1054)
      - Kansas City Art Institute - Video Curriculum (Evaluation), 1976, 1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 152, Folder 1055)
      - Kansas City Art Institute - Video Curriculum: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 152, Folder 1056)
      - KQED - "Media Probes", 1976, 1978-1981, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 1057-1058)
        Folder 1057 contains Evaluation
      - Kendrick, John, 1977-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1059)
      - Kendrick, John (Box T1)
        Audio cassette - John Kendrick - Poetry Folk Songs, Carl Kaye - Guitar, Vienna 1981
        Conditions Governing Access
        Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
      - Kendrick, John (Evaluation), 1978-1979 (Box 153, Folder 1060)
      - Kendrick, John: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 153, Folder 1061-1062, Box 154, Folder 1063)
      - Kineholistics Foundation, Inc. - Clarke, Wendy, 1977-1982 (Box 154, Folder 1064-1065)
      - Kubota, Shigeko, 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 1066)
        Folder 1066 contains Evaluation
      - Kubota, Shigeko: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 154, Folder 1067-1068, Box 155, Folder 1069)
      - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. - Humanities Institute, 1979-1984 (Box 155, Folder 1070)
        Folder 1070 contains Evaluation
      - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. - Humanities Institute: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 155, Folder 1071-1072)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video Project (I), 1975-1977, 1980, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 1073)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video Project (II), 1974-1982 (Box 155, Folder 1074-1075)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video Project (Evaluation), 1975, 1980 (Box 155, Folder 1076)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video Project: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 156, Folder 1077-1080)
      - Louisiana State University - "Television's Vietnam: The Impact of Visual Images", 1979-1985 (Box 156, Folder 1081-1082)
      - Macbeth, Robert, 1977-1982 (Box 157, Folder 1083)
      - Macbeth, Robert (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 157, Folder 1084)
      - Magic Theatre, Inc. - New Works, 1977-1983 (Box 157, Folder 1085-1086)
      - Magic Theatre, Inc. - New Works (Evaluation), 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 157, Folder 1087)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Artists' Fellowships, 1977-1981 (Box 157, Folder 1088-1089)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Artists' Fellowships (Evaluation), 1978, 1980-1983 (Box 157, Folder 1090)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Artists' Fellowships: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 157, Folder 1091, Box 158, Folder 1092-1096, Box 159, Folder 1097-1098, Box 158A, Folder 1096A)
      - Naropa Institute - Poetry Programs, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 1099)
        Folder 1099 contains Evaluation
      - Naropa Institute - Poetry Programs: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 159, Folder 1100-1101)
      - National Academy of Sciences - China Visit, 1976, 1980-1983 (Box 159, Folder 1102)
        Folder 1102 contains Evaluation
      - National Academy of Sciences - China Visit: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 160, Folder 1103-1104)
      - National Academy of Sciences - History and Philosophy of Science, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 1105-1106)
      - National Academy of Sciences - History and Philosophy of Science (Evaluation), 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 160, Folder 1107)
      - National Black Touring Circuit, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 160, Folder 1108)
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues (I), 1975-1979 (Box 161, Folder 1109)
        National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues (II), 1974-1980 (Box 161, Folder 1110-1112)
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues (Evaluation), 1975-1976, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 161, Folder 1113)
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 161, Folder 1114)
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: World Council of Churches, Geneva, Dr. W. A. Visser t'Hooft, G. Grose, A. M Biali, 6/27/75
        Access copy currently unavailablel Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
      - National Council of Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: Dr. W. A. Visser t'Hooft, Geo. Grose, A. M. Biali, Geneva, WCC, 1/27/75
      - New England Conservatory of Music - American Chamber Music, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1115)
        Folder 1115 contains Evaluation
      - New York Community Trust - Center for Communication, 1980-1982 (Box 161, Folder 1116)
      - New York University - Artists Workshop, 1979-1981 (Box 162, Folder 1117)
      - New York University - Artists Workshop (Evaluation), 1981, 1983 (Box 162, Folder 1118)
      - New York University - Telecommunications, 1976-1982 (Box 162, Folder 1119-1120)
      - New York University - Telecommunications (Evaluation), 1978-1980 (Box 162, Folder 1121)
      - New York University - Telecommunications: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 162, Folder 1122-1123)
      - North Carolina Dance Theater - Choreographers, 1979-1984 (Box 163, Folder 1124-1125)
        Folder 1124 contains Evaluation
      - Oklahoma State University - "Television's Vietnam", 1978-1979 (Box 163, Folder 1126)
      - Paperback Television, Inc. - Pilot Program, 1977-1982 (Box 163, Folder 1127-1128)
      - Paperback Television, Inc. - Pilot Program (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 163, Folder 1129)
      - Perspectives International, Inc. - History of Black American Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box 164, Folder 1130-1131)
        Folder 1130 contains Evaluation
      - Perspectives International, Inc. - History of Black American Colleges: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 164, Folder 1132-1133)
      - Raymond, Alan, 1978-1983 (Box 164, Folder 1134)
        Grant made to Susan and Alan Raymond
      - Rodgers Dance Company - New Works, 1978-1983 (Box 165, Folder 1135)
        Rod Rodgers Dance Company, Inc.
      - San Francisco Video Artists, 1978 (Box 165, Folder 1136)
      - San Francisco Video Artists (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 165, Folder 1137)
      - S.E.M. Ensemble - South American Tour, 1978-1981, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 1138)
        Folder 1138 contains Evaluation
      - Smithsonian Institution - History and Policy Analysis Conference, 1977-1981 (Box 165, Folder 1139)
      - Smithsonian Institution - History and Policy Analysis Conference (Evaluation), 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 1140)
      - Smithsonian Institution - History and Policy Analysis Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 165, Folder 1141-1142)
      - Snyder, Robert, 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 1143)
        Folder 1143 contains Evaluation
      - Solaris Dance Theater - Native American Dance, 1979-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1144)
      - State University of New York - American Modern Dance Festival, 1980-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1145-1146)
      - Stuart, Martha, 1979-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1147-1149)
      - Theatre Communications Group - Plays in Process, 1978-1983 (Box 167, Folder 1150-1151)
        Folder 1150 contains Evaluation
      - Theatre Communications Group - Plays in Process: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 167, Folder 1152-1153)
      - University of California, Berkeley - Douglas Oral History Project, 1974-1976, 1978-1982 (Box 167, Folder 1154)
        Helen Gahagan Douglas Oral History Project
      - University of California, Berkeley - Douglas Oral History Project (Evaluation), 1975, 1981, 1983 (Box 167, Folder 1155)
      - University of California, San Diego - Music Center, 1968-1982 (Box 168, Folder 1156-1160, Box 169, Folder 1161-1162)
        Folder 1156 contains Evaluation
      - University of California, San Diego - Music Center: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 169, Folder 1163-1166, Box 170, Folder 1167-1168)
        Folder 1168 - Computer Sound Demo Tape - Tracks from "the serpent-snapping eye" and "Voicespace III: The Palace," by R. Reynolds
      - University of California, Santa Barbara - Public History Conference, 1978-1982 (Box 170, Folder 1169-1170)
      - University of California, Santa Barbara - Public History Conference (Evaluation), 1978, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 1171)
      - University of California, Santa Barbara - Public History Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 170, Folder 1172-1173, Box 171, Folder 1174)
      - University of Connecticut - Cities Conference, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 1175)
        Folder 1175 contains Evaluation
      - University of La Verne - Padua Hills Writers Workshop, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 1176)
        Folder 1176 contains Evaluation
      - University of Maryland - National Boundary Problems, 1979-1981 (Box 171, Folder 1177)
      - University of North Carolina - American Comparative Literature Association (ACLA), 1979-1982 (Box 171, Folder 1178)
        Folder 1178 contains Evaluation
      - University of North Carolina - American Comparative Literature Association (ACLA): Supplementary Material, undated (Box 171, Folder 1179)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Humanistic Perspective, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 172, Folder 1180)
        Folder 1180 contains Evaluation
      - University of Southern California - Authority Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 172, Folder 1181)
        Folder 1181 contains Evaluation
      - University of Southern California - Authority Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 172, Folder 1182-1183)
      - Urban Communications Group - Rosa Parks Film, 1980-1983 (Box 172, Folder 1184)
        Folder 1184 contains Evaluation
      - Urban Communications Group - Rosa Parks Film: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 173, Folder 1185)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Roemer, Michael, 1978-1982 (Box 173, Folder 1186)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Workshop (I), 1974-1977, 1979-1982 (Box 173, Folder 1187)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Workshop (II), 1973-1983 (Box 173, Folder 1188-1190, Box 174, Folder 1191-1192)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Workshop (Evaluation), 1976, 1980-1983 (Box 174, Folder 1193)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Workshop: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 174, Folder 1194)
      - WQED - Media Probes, 1981-1983 (Box 174, Folder 1195)
      - WQED - Media Probes: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 174, Folder 1196)
      - Wayne State University - Black English Conference, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 174, Folder 1197, Box 175, Folder 1198-1200)
        Folder 1197 contains Evaluation
      - Yale University - Media Design (I), 1975, 1978-1979, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 1201)
      - Yale University - Media Design (II), 1974-1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 175, Folder 1202-1203, Box 176, Folder 1204)
      - Yale University - Media Design (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 176, Folder 1205)
      - Yale University - Media Design: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 176, Folder 1206)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Asia Society - China Council, 1975-1976, 1979-1980 (Box 176, Folder 1207)
      - Asia Society - China Council (Evaluation), 1976 (Box 176, Folder 1208)
      - Asia Society - China Council: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 176, Folder 1209-1210, Box 177, Folder 1211)
      - Brandeis University - Youth Employment, 1979-1981 (Box 177, Folder 1212)
        Folder 1212 contains Evaluation
      - Education Issues Conference, 1981 (Box 177, Folder 1213)
        Rockefeller Foundation National Conference on Education Issues, October 13-14, 1981
      - Guttmacher Institute - Abortion Study, 1977-1981 (Box 177, Folder 1214-1215)
      - Guttmacher Institute - Abortion Study (Evaluation), 1977 (Box 177, Folder 1216)
      - Harvard University - Indonesian Textbook, 1977-1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 178, Folder 1217)
      - Harvard University - Indonesian Textbook (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 178, Folder 1218)
      - Kuenne, Robert E., 1976-1981 (Box 178, Folder 1219)
        Study title: "A Model of the OPEC Cartel"
      - Kuenne, Robert E. (Evaluation), 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 178, Folder 1220)
      - Kuenne, Robert E.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 178, Folder 1221-1222)
      - League of Women Voters Education Fund - Federal Revenue Sharing, 1979-1981 (Box 178, Folder 1223)
        Folder 1223 contains Evaluation
      - League of Women Voters Education Fund - Federal Revenue Sharing: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 178, Folder 1224, Box 179, Folder 1225)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Economic Analysis of Human Behavior and Social Institutions, 1972-1977, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 1226-1228)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Economic Analysis of Human Behavior and Social Institutions (Evaluation), 1972, 1976 (Box 179, Folder 1229)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Economic Analysis of Human Behavior and Social Institutions: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 180, Folder 1230-1232, Box 181, Folder 1233)
      - Northwestern University - Male Youth Employment, 1978-1982 (Box 181, Folder 1234-1235)
      - Puerto Rican Migration Research Consortium - Employment Study, 1976-1982 (Box 181, Folder 1236-1237)
      - Rand Corporation - Fertility and Health Variables, 1972-1983 (Box 182, Folder 1238-1243, Box 183, Folder 1244-1245)
      - Rand Corporation - Fertility and Health Variables (Evaluation), 1976, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 1246)
      - Rand Corporation - Fertility and Health Variables: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 183, Folder 1247-1251, Box 184, Folder 1252-1257, Box 185, Folder 1258-1262, Box 186, Folder 1263-1265)
      - University of Chicago - Food Security, 1979-1982, 1986 (Box 186, Folder 1266)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Asian Rice Economy, 1977, 1979-1981 (Box 186, Folder 1267)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Asian Rice Economy (Evaluation), 1977 (Box 186, Folder 1268)
      - Whiteford, Michael B., 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 186, Folder 1269, Box 187, Folder 1270)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, W
      - New York University, 1978-1982 (Box 187, Folder 1271-1272)
        Folder 1271 contains Evaluation
  - Fellowships in Administration of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs, 267
    - Fellowships in Administration of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs, 1976-1979, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 1273)
    - Maryland, 223
      - Cooper, Charlene, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 187, Folder 1274)
        Folder 1274 contains Evaluation
    - North Carolina, 236
      - Watts, Velma Gibson, 1978-1982 (Box 187, Folder 1275)
        Folder 1275 contains Evaluation
    - Pennsylvania, 241
      - Brewer, Jeanette W., 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 187, Folder 1276)
        Folder 1276 contains Evaluation
      - Clayton, Constance E., 1977, 1979-1983 (Box 188, Folder 1277)
        Folder 1277 contains Evaluation
  - Fellowships in Finance and Management in Higher and Secondary Education for Minority-Group Educators, 268
    - Fellowships in Finance and Management in Higher and Secondary Education for Minority-Group Educators, 1974-1979, 1982 (Box 188, Folder 1278)
    - Fellowships in Finance and Management in Higher and Secondary Education for Minority-Group Educators: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 188, Folder 1279)
    - Fellowships, E
      - Columbia University, 1977-1982 (Box 188, Folder 1280)
        Folder 1280 contains Evaluation
      - Isom, Deborah A., 1977-1981 (Box 188, Folder 1281)
        Folder 1281 contains Evaluation
      - Lopez, Fidel, 1977-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 188, Folder 1282)
      - Lopez, Fidel (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 188, Folder 1283)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects and Activities in the Southeastern Region of the United States, 275
    - Historically Black Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box 189, Folder 1284-1285)
    - Historically Black Colleges - Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 189, Folder 1286)
    - Mississippi Research and Development Center, 1975-1983 (Box 189, Folder 1287-1288)
      Folder 1287 contains Evaluation
    - Mississippi Research and Development Center (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 190, Folder 1289)
    - Mississippi Research and Development Center: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 190, Folder 1290)
    - Virginia State College - Community Development, 1975-1980, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 1291-1294)
    - Virginia State College - Community Development (Evaluation), 1976, 1978, 1983 (Box 190, Folder 1295)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - Columbia University - Urban Labor Markets, 1980-1982 (Box 190, Folder 1296, Box 191, Folder 1297)
    - Columbia University - Urban Labor Markets: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 191, Folder 1298)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - Private Sector Wage Subsidy, 1978, 1980-1983 (Box 191, Folder 1299-1301)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - Private Sector Wage Subsidy: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 191, Folder 1302-1303, Box 192, Folder 1304-1309, Box 193, Folder 1310-1315, Box 194, Folder 1316-1320, Box 195, Folder 1321-1326, Box 196, Folder 1327-1332, Box 197, Folder 1333-1339, Box 198, Folder 1340-1345, Box 199, Folder 1346-1351, Box 200, Folder 1352-1357, Box 201, Folder 1358-1361)
    - National Council on Employment Policy - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Program Review, 1979-1981 (Box 201, Folder 1362)
    - National Council on Employment Policy - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Program Review: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 201, Folder 1363, Box 202, Folder 1364-1365)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Youth Unemployment, 1979-1981 (Box 202, Folder 1366)
  - Training in Museum Education, 280
    - Museum Education Training - Minutes, 1969, 1972-1980 (Box 202, Folder 1367)
    - Museum Education Training, 1972-1979, 1981 (Box 202, Folder 1368-1370, Box 203, Folder 1371-1372)
    - Museum Education Training (Evaluation), 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 203, Folder 1373)
    - Museum Education Training: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 203, Folder 1374-1375)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1972-1982 (Box 203, Folder 1376, Box 204, Folder 1377-1382, Box 205, Folder 1383-1386)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Evaluation), 1976, 1978 (Box 205, Folder 1387)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 205, Folder 1388, Box 206, Folder 1389-1392)
    - Walker Art Center, 1970-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 206, Folder 1393-1394)
    - Walker Art Center (Evaluation), 1976; 1978; 1980-1981 (Box 206, Folder 1395)
  - Ethnic Archives of American Immigrant Groups, 285
    - Ethnic Archives Development Program, 1969, 1977-1981 (Box 207, Folder 1396)
    - Kent State University - Non-Slavic Archive Cataloging, 1979-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 207, Folder 1397)
    - Pilsudski Institute of America - Polish Archive, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 207, Folder 1398)
      Folder 1398 contains Evaluation
    - University of Alabama - Ethnic Minority Archives, 1977-1981. 1983 (Box 207, Folder 1399)
      Folder 1399 contains Evaluation
    - University of Alabama - Ethnic Minority Archives: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 207, Folder 1400-1401)
  - Latin America, 300
    - Latin America - Social Sciences, S
      - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (IICA) - Human Resources, 1977-1981 (Box 207, Folder 1402-1403, Box 208, Folder 1404-1405)
        Instituto Interamericano de Ciencias Agricolas (IICA)
      - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (IICA) - Human Resources (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 208, Folder 1406)
      - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (IICA) - Human Resources: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 208, Folder 1407-1409, Box 209, Folder 1410-1413)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, A
      - Parasite Immunology in Bahia - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 209, Folder 1414)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Congregaҫão Mariana Universitária - Fishery, 1979-1982 (Box 209, Folder 1415-1416)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Almeida Filho, Naomar Monteiro de, 1976-1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 1417-1418)
      - Azevêdo, José Sérgio Gabrielli de, 1975-1982 (Box 210, Folder 1419)
      - Lins, Roberto D'Oliveira, 1979-1982 (Box 210, Folder 1420)
    - Brazil - University Development, UD
      - University of Bahia - Beans, Wheat and Rice, 1976-1980 (Box 210, Folder 1421)
      - University of Bahia - Beans, Wheat and Rice (Evaluation), 1976, 1978, 1980 (Box 210, Folder 1422)
      - University of Bahia - Oysterculture, 1976-1982 (Box 210, Folder 1423)